<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="ACE">
    <Package name="bullettracker">
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_bullettracker_MaxTrackPerFrame">
            <English>Maximum Projectiles Per Frame</English>
            <Spanish>Máximos proyectiles por cuadro</Spanish>
            <German>Maximale Anzahl an Projektilen pro Frame</German>
            <Polish>Maks. liczba pocisków na klatkę</Polish>
            <Czech>Maximální počet projektilů za jeden snímek</Czech>
            <Portuguese>Projéteis máximos por quadro</Portuguese>
            <French>Nombre maximal de projectile par image</French>
            <Hungarian>Maximum repesz/képkocka</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Макс. количество снарядов за кадр</Russian>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="STR_ACE_bullettracker_MaxTrackPerFrame_Desc">
            <English>The number of spall track calculations to perform in any given frame. This helps spread the FPS impact of tracking spall rounds across multiple frames, limiting its impact even further.</English>
            <Polish>Ilość obliczeń wykonywanych przez symulację odprysków w danej klatce. Ta opcja pomaga rozprzestrzenić obliczenia odprysków na więcej klatek, zmniejszając spadek FPS jeszcze bardziej.</Polish>
            <German>Gibt die Anzahl der Explosionverfolgungsberechnungen an, die gleichzeitig ausgeführt werden. Das kann dabei helfen den FPS-Einfluss abzuschwächen, wenn Teile über mehrere Frames hinweg verfolgt werden.</German>
            <Spanish>El número de cálculos de esquirlas que se hará en cualquier cuadro. Esto ayuda a dispersar el impacto en FPS del seguimiento de esquirlas de balas a través de múltiples cuadros, lo que limita aún más su impacto.</Spanish>
            <Czech>Počet úlomků v daném snímku. Toto pomáhá rozšířit FPS dopad sledovaného úlomku napříč více snímky, omezuje jeho vliv ještě více.</Czech>
            <Portuguese>O número de cálculos por estilhaço rastreado para executar em qualquer quadro. Isso ajuda a distribuir o impacto no FPS do rastreamento de estilhaço em vários quadros, o que limita o seu impacto ainda mais.</Portuguese>
            <French>Le nombre d'éclat à calculer dans chaque images. Ceci permet de diffuser l'impact sur les FPS dans de multiples images, le limitant d'autant plus.</French>
            <Hungarian>A lepattogzási útvonalak számításának darabjai képkockánként. Ez eloszlatja az FPS-megszakadást több képkockára, ezzel csökkentve a súlyosságát.</Hungarian>
            <Russian>Число обрабатываемых осколков за кадр. Это позволяет распределить нагрузку по отслеживанию осколков между несколькими кадрами, чтобы предотвратить падение FPS.</Russian>
        </Key>
    </Package>
</Project>
